Class of 1884 Records, 1876-1955
Smith College Archives
Class of 1884 Records
1876-1955
Smith College. Class of 1884.
RG 80 UUID:696f58c7-d144-4a58-b683-836a3f0c6fa4
4 boxes (2.75 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains black and white photographs, invitations, programs, letters, correspondence, diaries, and information about the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1884.
The Class of 1884 was the sixth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1884 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1884. Types of materials include black and white photographs, invitations, programs, letters, correspondence, diaries, and information about the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1884.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1884 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1884: Baccalaureate Service 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 1)
- Class of 1884: Class Book 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 2)
- Class of 1884: Commencement 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 3)
- Class of 1884: Commencement Music 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 4)
- Class of 1884: Commencement Speaker 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 5)
- Class of 1884: Composite Photographs (Box 1415, Folder 6)
- Class of 1884: Groups 1882, 1884, 1887 (Box 1415, Folder 7)
- Class of 1884: History undated (Box 1415, Folder 8)
- Class of 1884: Ivy Day undated (Box 1415, Folder 9)
- Class of 1884: Organization 1880-89, 1891-94, 1898-99, 1904, 1906-35, 1937, 1941 (Box 1415, Folder 10)
- Class of 1884: Reunions (Miscellaneous) undated (Box 1415, Folder 11)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1889) 1889 (Box 1415, Folder 12)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1894) 1894 (Box 1415, Folder 13)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1909) 1909 (Box 1415, Folder 14)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1914) 1914 (Box 1415, Folder 15)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1924) 1924 (Box 1415, Folder 16)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1925) 1925 (Box 1415, Folder 17)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1929) 1929 (Box 1415, Folder 18)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1934) 1934 (Box 1415, Folder 19)
- Class of 1884: Reunion (1939) 1939 (Box 1415, Folder 20)
- Class of 1884: Reunion Songs undated (Box 1415, Folder 21)
- Class of 1884: Senior Dramatics 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 22)
- Class of 1884: Senior Reception 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 23)
- Class of 1884: Songs 1883-84, 1914, undated (Box 1415, Folder 24)
- Class of 1884: Sophomore Reception 1880 (Box 1415, Folder 25)
- Class of 1884: Sophomore-Senior Reception for 1882 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 26)
- Class of 1884: Class Supper 1884 (Box 1415, Folder 27)
- Class of 1884: Adams, Margaret 1880 (Box 1416, Folder 1)
- Class of 1884: Allis, Annie Amelia 1884, 1895, 1897, 1944, undated (Box 1416, Folder 2)
- Class of 1884: Allis, Fannie Augusta (Letters) 1881, 1917, 1931, 1936 (Box 1416, Folder 3)
- Class of 1884: Allis, Fannie Augusta (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 4)
- Class of 1884: Austin, Jennie Maude (Correspondence) 1882 (Box 1416, Folder 5)
- Class of 1884: Austin, Jennie Maude (Photographs) 1883, undated (Box 1416, Folder 6)
- Class of 1884: Barton, Mary Louisa (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 7)
- Class of 1884: Brooks, Annie Smith (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 8)
- Class of 1884: Bullen, Charlotte Packard 1882 (Box 1416, Folder 9)
- Class of 1884: Campbell, Mary B. (Photographs, etc) 1944, undated (Box 1416, Folder 10)
- Class of 1884: Clark, Ella Cleveland undated (Box 1416, Folder 11)
- Class of 1884: Clough, Marion Belmont (Photographs, etc) 1885, undated (Box 1416, Folder 12)
- Class of 1884: Connely, Bertha Lillian (Box 1416, Folder 13)
- Class of 1884: Cox, Martha Lyman (Photographs, etc) 1936, undated (Box 1416, Folder 14)
- Class of 1884: Crowell, Mary Savage (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 15)
- Class of 1884: Delano, Sally Haskell (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 16)
- Class of 1884: Duguid, Mary Evelyn (Box 1416, Folder 17)
- Class of 1884: Dunn, Kate Clark (Photographs) 1884, undated (Box 1416, Folder 18)
- Class of 1884: Fisk, Nina Perry (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 19)
- Class of 1884: French, Clara (Photographs, etc) 1892, undated (Box 1416, Folder 20)
- Class of 1884: Gladden, Alice (Correspondence) 1884-87, 1898, undated (Box 1416, Folder 21)
- Class of 1884: Gladden, Alice (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 22)
- Class of 1884: Herrick, Harriet Fidelia (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 23)
- Class of 1884: Heywood, Lucy Florence 1884, 1944, 1949, undated (Box 1416, Folder 24)
- Class of 1884: Jameson, Katharine Strong (Photographs, etc) 1882-83, 1940, undated (Box 1416, Folder 25)
- Class of 1884: Johnson, Mary Augusta (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 26)
- Class of 1884: Kelsey, Louise Hoyt (Photographs) 1883-84, undated (Box 1416, Folder 27)
- Class of 1884: King, Mary Emma (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 28)
- Class of 1884: Lacey, Caroline Elvira (Photographs) 1876, 1880 (Box 1416, Folder 29)
- Class of 1884: Martin (Irwin-Martin), Jeanne Clark (Photographs) 1884 (Box 1416, Folder 30)
- Class of 1884: Mason, Mary Lyman (Diary) 1897 (Box 1416, Folder 31)
- Class of 1884: Mason, Mary Lyman (Photographs, etc) undated (Box 1416, Folder 32)
- Class of 1884: Mead, Lydia Abigail (Correspondence) 1884 (Box 1416, Folder 33)
- Class of 1884: Mead, Lydia Abigail (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 34)
- Class of 1884: Mehan, Alida Mary (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 35)
- Class of 1884: Merriam, Betsey Greene (Correspondence) 1896, 1944 (Box 1416, Folder 36)
- Class of 1884: Merriam, Betsey Greene (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 37)
- Class of 1884: Mills, Alice Mountfort (Photographs) undated (Box 1416, Folder 38)
- Class of 1884: Morse, Jane Cora (Photographs, etc) 1882, 1884, undated (Box 1416, Folder 39)
- Class of 1884: Paddock, Ida Imogene (Photographs) 1883-84 (Box 1417, Folder 1)
- Class of 1884: Parks, Jessie Ellis (Photographs) 1881, undated (Box 1417, Folder 2)
- Class of 1884: Perkins, Ella Augusta (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 3)
- Class of 1884: Rand, Helen Chadwick 1915, undated (Box 1417, Folder 4)
- Class of 1884: Rand, Helen Chadwick (Correspondence) 1884-86, 1889, 1892, 1904 (Box 1417, Folder 5)
- Class of 1884: Richardson, Carrie Lavinia (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 6)
- Class of 1884: Richardson, Jennie May (Photographs, etc) 1944, undated (Box 1417, Folder 7)
- Class of 1884: Rogers, Harriet Clara (Special) (Photographs) 1882 (Box 1417, Folder 8)
- Class of 1884: Rogers, Mary Grace (Photographs) 1882-83, undated (Box 1417, Folder 9)
- Class of 1884: Rose, Marion Elizabeth (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 10)
- Class of 1884: Scudder, Vida Dutton (Box 1417, Folder 11)
- Class of 1884: Seelye, Elizabeth James (Diaries and Course Notes) 1880-90, undated (Box 1417, Folder 12)
- Class of 1884: Seelye, Elizabeth James (Photographs, etc) 1880-81, undated (Box 1417, Folder 13)
- Class of 1884: Sergeant, Caroline Belle 1944 (Box 1417, Folder 14)
- Class of 1884: Sergeant, Caroline Belle (Photographs, etc) 1955, undated (Box 1417, Folder 15)
- Class of 1884: Seymour, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs) 1881, undated (Box 1417, Folder 16)
- Class of 1884: Sheldon, Helen Mary 1944, undated (Box 1417, Folder 17)
- Class of 1884: Skilton, Ida Galpin (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 18)
- Class of 1884: Smith, Flora Ella (Photographs) 1881-82 (Box 1417, Folder 19)
- Class of 1884: Stevens, Mary Louisa (Photographs) 1884, undated (Box 1417, Folder 20)
- Class of 1884: Taylor, Agnes Louise (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 21)
- Class of 1884: Tiemann, Elsie Claire (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 22)
- Class of 1884: Trafton, Mary Adelaide (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 23)
- Class of 1884: Tyler, Frances Maria (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 24)
- Class of 1884: Whitten, Helen Frances (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 25)
- Class of 1884: Wood, Mina Emma (Photographs) undated (Box 1417, Folder 26)
- Class of 1884: Wright, Elizabeth Antoinette 1883 (Box 1417, Folder 27)
- Class of 1884: Duguid, Mary Evelyn (Photographs) 1880, 1882-84, undated (Box 1418, Folder 1)
- Class of 1884: Duguid, Mary Evelyn (Scrapbook) Various dates (Box 1418)